???: Making a child cry... What a shame on you, VICCARI!
Luiza: Why do I have to run into you on my way instead of finding money every time?
Neftari: Oh, JOÃO again? Get out of the way, you're not an X-Men to go through people!
João: VICCARI, I came to challenge you since you're so tough to pick on a child. Beat me, let's battle!
Neftari: Now I like this, let's go then, BERTINAZZI.
Bertinazzi: Haha... AHAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH!!
Marcus Vinícius: What?
Luiza: Look over there, didn't take your medicine, you're affected.
Bertinazzi: I knew it! I knew it, VICCARI, you're a worthy rival.
Neftari: Me?
Bertinazzi: Yes, you see, your family is VICCARI, and I'm from the Bertinazzi family. Our families have been historical rivals, even before immigrating from Italy.
Bertinazzi: I always knew that one day we would face each other, you know, it's destiny, and well, that day has come.
Neftari: But you were the one waiting for me here.
Bertinazzi: I'll see you around, VICCARI!
Neftari: I hope not.
Luiza: Is it true? Your families have been rivals since Italy? Isn't that the plot of a famous soap opera?
Neftari: I don't know; I just know my grandfather's name was Gersom.
Marcus Vinícius: Back in the town where I was born, MANDIOQUINHA, there were two rival bakers. They were always competing to see who sold the best bread.
Marcus Vinícius: Until the people of MANDIOQUINHA got so tired of their rivalry that they decided to join forces and conduct a test,
Marcus Vinícius: A bunch of blindfolded people tasted the bread, and they decided which one was the best. When the results came out, the baker who lost,
Marcus Vinícius: Didn't want to accept it. He said he would only acknowledge his defeat over his dead body.
Luiza: And then? What happened next?
Marcus Vinícius: Someone granted his request and shot him.
Luiza: Why did I even ask? Let's hurry up and buy that wax.
Shirley: Luiza, thank goodness I found you; your neighbors are fighting again.
Luiza: I'm heading over there; I can't miss yesterday's continuation. Don't count on me for anything.