Luíza: Hey Nef, let's go to the machine circus; I think it's about to open soon.
Neftari: Hmm, I don't know; the FantoRob championship starts today, and I need to go to the opening.
Luíza: What time is the opening?
Neftari: In a little while.
Luíza: Then let's go to the circus right now.
Neftari: Oh no, it doesn't seem very grown-up.
Luíza: Come oooon, please! Marcus is already waiting for us there, in the name of friendship.
Neftari: Sigh, okay, in the name of friendship.