Luiza: NEF, let's go to the Machine Circus; it seems to be working now.
Neftari: Oh, you're not gonna drag me there again, are you?
Marcus Vinícius: Uai, didn't you make a deal with the owner for him to help you? He told you to come back every time you won a challenge.
Luiza: Come on, we're going... Is that Caseiro Róger over there?
Scared Boy: Go, uncle, go!
Neftari: What are you doing here?
Caseiro Róger: Howdy, y'all. I was talkin' 'bout the DEVIL'S PUPPET.
Marcus Vinícius: Here we go again, what's this DEVIL'S PUPPET?
Caseiro Róger: I was out there on my farm takin' care of my cows...
Luiza: Marcus, why did you ask?
Caseiro Róger: Then I go like SQUAAAAAAAASH SQUAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAASH.
Caseiro Róger: So I said:
Caseiro Róger: HOLY MARY, I'M GONNA SHOOT!
Caseiro Róger: Then I heard
Caseiro Róger: PLEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEENT PLEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEENT.
Caseiro Róger:...
Neftari:...
Caseiro Róger:...
Luiza:...
Caseiro Róger: Y'all payin' attention?
Neftari: Go on.
Caseiro Róger: So I said:
Caseiro Róger: AJISDGJAOGJLDOJAPGJO I'M ALMOST SHOOTIN'!
Caseiro Róger: Then I saw right in front of me, right in front of me....
Luiza: A painted jaguar.
Caseiro Róger: Uai, how'd you know?
Neftari: Well, I think this DEVIL'S PUPPET story is just a lie of yours!
Caseiro Róger: No, the DEVIL'S PUPPET does exist, I got proof!
Scared Girl: It's true, we were at the little farm picking mangoes just now, and we saw it.
Marcus Vinícius: Saw what?
Scared Boy: The DEVIL'S PUPPET! It was in the middle of the trees, watchin' us. I got so scared, I dropped the mangoes and ran.
Scared Girl: Now we're askin' this fella to go check, and he doesn't wanna.
Caseiro Róger: I don't, I'm scared of these DEVIL'S PUPPET things.
Neftari: Alright, we'll go take a look. Wait here.
Marcus Vinícius: Are we going?
Neftari: I wanna find out what this DEVIL'S PUPPET is!
Marcus Vinícius: But, but...
Luiza: Come on, don't turn into a coward like that bumpkin over there.
Caseiro Róger: Hey!