Narrator: And after the electrifying previous battle, let's move on to the second battle of this final!
Narrator: On one side, we have Diego Brandão!
Narrator: Will he manage to advance and get the chance for revenge?
Narrator: On the other side, we have E-Sarah!
Narrator: Who claims to be ready to thwart that revenge. Will her next post be victorious or defeated?
E-Sarah: Everyone here is rooting for you. It'll be a shame to disappoint their expectations, you know?
E-Sarah: But today, you'll pay for what you did to Preá!
Neftari: ...You're just trying to grab attention.
Narrator: And... FIGHT!