Roberta: I'm passionate about the art of assembling FantoRobs, and I'm always here at FantoLab, observing the newbies.
Roberta: My name is Roberta.
Roberta: When customizing a FantoRob, it's essential to pay attention to the part you're attaching.
Roberta: Different parts have different compilers, which can impact the part's performance.
Roberta: It's not too difficult; you just need to pay close attention to the information the console is providing.
Roberta: If you understood, clap your hands; if you didn't, well, patience.