Marcus Vinícius: Each FantoRob has two status bars!
Marcus Vinícius: Let's start with the RES bar, which represents resistance.
Marcus Vinícius: This bar indicates the FantoRob's defense.
Marcus Vinícius: It represents how much the FantoRob can RESIST attacks it receives.
Marcus Vinícius: When it starts getting attacked, this bar begins to decrease.
Marcus Vinícius: The lower it goes, the less the FantoRob can resist attacks.
Marcus Vinícius: When this bar becomes NEGATIVE, we usually say the FantoRob is BROKEN.
Marcus Vinícius: In this state, it will start regenerating the resistance bar back to its maximum.
Marcus Vinícius: However, while it's regenerating, it becomes weak, and all damage it receives from attacks...
Marcus Vinícius: Goes to INTEGRITY, which leads us to our second bar.
Marcus Vinícius: The INT bar represents that integrity, and it's quite simple to understand.
Marcus Vinícius: If a FantoRob's INT reaches ZERO, it is out of the fight.
Marcus Vinícius: It's like their "LIFE." If it runs out, they "DIE."
Marcus Vinícius: Lastly, we have the BATTERY.
Marcus Vinícius: FantoRob has BATTERY, and as it attacks, it depletes the battery.
Marcus Vinícius: If the BATTERY reaches ZERO, it also becomes incapacitated, just like if INT reaches zero.