Marcus Vinícius: Now, let's analyze the attack properties.
Marcus Vinícius: First is STR, which indicates the strength of an attack.
Marcus Vinícius: Then there's ACC, which indicates accuracy, meaning the chance of not missing.
Marcus Vinícius: Now, there's ENERG, which indicates the BATTERY COST of a FantoRob.
Marcus Vinícius: Remember, if a FantoRob's BATTERY reaches ZERO, it becomes INCAPACITATED.