Marcus Vinícius: Let's take a look at ACTIONS.
Marcus Vinícius: At the top, you can see the number of ACTIONS an attack SPENDS.
Marcus Vinícius: Notice those BLUE BARS at the bottom? They represent ACTIONS.
Marcus Vinícius: When a FantoRob attacks, it EXPENDS ACTIONS.
Marcus Vinícius: When the actions reach ZERO, it ENDS THE TURN and needs to wait.
Marcus Vinícius: At least ONE to RECHARGE to do anything again.
Marcus Vinícius: ACTIONS recharge when the FantoRob is IDLE without doing anything in combat.
Marcus Vinícius: According to the SPEED of a FantoRob.
Marcus Vinícius: The faster it is, the faster it recharges ACTIONS.
Marcus Vinícius: This means that if a FantoRob is very fast, it can attack twice in a row!