Marcus ViníciMarcus Vinícius: Every FantoRob has two cores: ELEMENTAL on the left and PHYSICAL on the right.
Marcus Vinícius: They impact the battle calculations based on their compatibility.
Marcus Vinícius: ELEMENTAL cores have an ADVANTAGEOUS relationship between them.
Marcus Vinícius: PHYSICAL cores have a DISADVANTAGEOUS relationship between them.
Marcus Vinícius: Besides affecting battle damage, the PHYSICAL CORE has functions in battles that can be used to gain an advantage.
Marcus Vinícius: This is the PHYSICAL CORE BUTTON, used to activate this function.
Marcus Vinícius: Your GIRINOROB has a cutting PHYSICAL core, and its button activates FRENZY; just press it.
Marcus Vinícius: To understand all the physical cores and what they do, you'll need to read the manuals later on.