Marcus Vinícius: When your FantoRob is being attacked, you can try to reduce or avoid the damage.
Marcus Vinícius: To do this, you need to pay attention to the attack.
Marcus Vinícius: PHYSICAL attacks can be DEFLECTED, meaning the damage to resistance is reduced.
Marcus Vinícius: When you see this sign and hear this sound.
Marcus Vinícius:
Marcus Vinícius: You must quickly press the RIGHT MOUSE BUTTON; if you hit it, you'll hear this sound.
Marcus Vinícius:
Marcus Vinícius: This means you DEFLECTED THE ATTACK.
Marcus Vinícius: ELEMENTAL attacks, on the other hand, can only be DODGED, which means the attack doesn't hit.
Marcus Vinícius: When you see this sign and hear this sound.
Marcus Vinícius:
Marcus Vinícius: You must quickly press the LEFT MOUSE BUTTON; if you hit it, you'll hear this sound.
Marcus Vinícius:
Marcus Vinícius: This means you INCREASED THE CHANCES of your FantoRob dodging the attack.