Neftari: Hey, what are you guys doing?
FantoMask1: Get lost, kid, this doesn't concern you!
Neftari: I'm not going to let you continue doing whatever you want!
João: I don't need your help, Viccari!
FantoMask1: Oh yeah? Well, now you're in this too!
FantoMask1: Uh, well, I've already done what I needed to do.
FantoMask2: Come on, let's get out of here!
João: I had already weakened him for you!
João: Who were those guys?
Neftari: I'm not entirely sure, but they're trying to manipulate the results of the championship.
Neftari: I was their target, and now it seems they've targeted you.
Neftari: There's no point in trying to report them; no one will believe it.
Neftari: To the championship organizers, they're just an excuse that losing participants use.
João: Tsk, they messed up my plans, my FantoRobs need repair.
João: I'll have to withdraw for now, but it's a strategic retreat.
João: Don't think for a second that you saved me, Viccari!
Neftari: I certainly won't.