Marcus Vinícius: Hey Nef, what happened? We were watching you on the stream, you were doing so well.
Marcus Vinícius: Then you disappeared, and when you came back, you were losing to João.
Luiza: It was quite humiliating.
Marcus Vinícius: Luiza!
Luiza: Well, do you want me to lie now?
Neftari: I was sabotaged.
Luiza: Oh, how so?
Neftari: I'm going to look for Mr. Oswaldo at the tower. If you want to come along, it's better because I'll tell the whole story.
Marcus Vinícius: Let's go then.