Marcus Vinícius: Congratulations, Nef, you did pretty well.
Marcus Vinícius: But unfortunately, you're still in the zone of the disqualified, right?
Luiza: It's been quite humiliating.
Marcus Vinícius: Luiza!
Luiza: Well, do you want me to lie now?
Neftari: I'm not giving up just yet.
Luiza: That's right, Nef, embarrass yourself without feeling embarrassed!
Neftari: I'm going to look for Mr. Oswaldo at the tower. If you guys want to come along.
Marcus Vinícius: Let's go then.