Neftari: Mr. Leonidas, what are you doing here?
Leonidas: Pedro! I was waiting for you to wish you good luck!
Neftari: Today, no one seems to get my name right. Who's Pedro?
Leonidas: Oh, I apologize. It's just that you remind me a lot of my younger brother. I'm really sorry.
Neftari: No problem, at least you didn't call me Diego Brandão.
Leonidas: Funny, I saw someone call you that in a video on the internet.
Leonidas: I imagine you must be so focused that you haven't seen it.
Neftari: I haven't, but I'll look it up later.
Leonidas: Okay, then tell me about it later. I'm curious!