FantoHelper: Who's ready?
FantoHelper: WHO'S READY?
FantoHelper: To live the most awaited moment of the WHOLE YEAR!
FantoHelper: Today is the day.
FantoHelper: TODAY IS THE DAY!
FantoHelper: Today, the masters will be tested to the limit!
FantoHelper: Eight enter as finalists, but only one emerges as the BEST IN THE WORLD!
FantoHelper: So, I'll ask again...
FantoHelper: WHO'S READY HERE?
FantoHelper: Now, entering the Arena, the EIGHT FINALISTS WHO WILL COMPETE IN THE FINAL!
Luiza: NEF! NEF! We're here, NEF!
Marcus Vinícius: I think he heard us; he looked at us!
Luiza: DON'T GET NERVOUS, NEF. IF YOU LOSE, YOU'LL JUST EMBARRASS YOURSELF NATIONWIDE.
Marcus Vinícius: Luiza!
Luiza: Uai, do you want me to lie?
Fantorob Company Employee: Keep moving, don't delay the entrance!
Neftari: Sorry.
FantoHelper: Now, let's meet our finalists!
FantoHelper: She secured her spot by gracefully dodging attacks like no other!
FantoHelper: ELIZAROB!
FantoHelper: He caught everyone's attention with his costume throughout the championship and managed to make it to the final in the last minute!
FantoHelper: CUEI!
FantoHelper: He's been the champion for the last three years and is here to defend his reign and prove he's still the best!
FantoHelper: PREÁ!
FantoHelper: He's made it to the final for five consecutive years! Is this the year he'll finally surpass himself and become the champion?
FantoHelper: ROCKCOOLCAT!
Neftari: (And Oswaldo had an issue with my name?)
FantoHelper: She's the queen, the dominator of live streams and reaction videos, and she's here to show that she's not just a pretty face!
FantoHelper: E-SARAH!
FantoHelper: The controversial, the divisive, a hero to many, an anime villain to many others, he's here to finally dethrone Preá!
FantoHelper: DIEGO BRANDÃO!
FantoHelper: She arrived here with her sweet demeanor and her beautiful white jumpsuit, but don't be mistaken; she won't give up the title easily!
FantoHelper: MONIQUINHA!
FantoHelper: Last but not least!
FantoHelper: He won the audience over with his deep green eyes and the already epic rivalry with Diego Brandão. Will he finally prove he's better?
FantoHelper: BERTIZZEIRA!
Neftari: (Uai?)
FantoHelper: And before we conclude this opening and get to what matters, I must salute her!
FantoHelper: The reason for all this, the reason why you and I are here!
FantoHelper: The one all the finalists want to raise!
FantoHelper: THE FANTOTROPHY!
FantoHelper: Folks, folks, get ready, fasten your seatbelts because I declare the FantoRob Championship final OPEN, and it's GOING TO BE EPIC!