Oswaldo: I didn't expect to see you here so soon. Did you get the two FantoRobs?
Neftari: Yes, I did.
Oswaldo: Then here's your endorsement letter.
Oswaldo:(Oswaldo handed over the ENDORSEMENT LETTER, and now you're participating in the FantoRob Championship.)
Oswaldo: Now, as protocol dictates, I'm obligated to give you some basic explanations, even though I assume you already know.
Oswaldo: The FantoRob Company's Summer Championship, which starts next week, takes place between January and February.
Oswaldo: Participants face 7 challenges, and within these challenges, you'll battle other participants...
Oswaldo: And the Masters of the FantoRob Company itself. Depending on the day you win, you'll be ranked,
Oswaldo: The sooner you finish, the more points you'll score.
Oswaldo: If you're defeated, you'll LOSE THE DAY and can only re-enter the next day.
Oswaldo: Your abilities will be tested to the extreme, and besides the challenge being designed to make you LOSE WITHIN IT...
Oswaldo: you cannot DECLINE A BATTLE!
Oswaldo: In the end, the top 8 finishers will participate in the final, which will take place at the FantoRob ARENA.
Oswaldo: The Championship is the main attraction in the country during the summer, so if you perform well...
Oswaldo: It will garner a lot of attention, besides the obvious fame, you can secure sponsors.
Oswaldo: So winning battles means getting more parts and money, which are essential to stay competitive.
Oswaldo: I won't lie; the Championship can be a bit stressful, but try to have fun, and good luck.
Neftari: Thank you; I'll do my best.