Preá: Get out of the way, professional coming through!
Neftari: Preá, um... I'm your fan. Do you have, like, some advice to give me?
Preá: I think it's very important to learn to accept your own limitations.
Preá: Second or third place is also great, even fourth is excellent for someone like you.
Preá: Now, excuse me, I'm going to be the first and finish this challenge.
Neftari: Well, you might not believe it, but I've already finished!
Preá: WHAT? Like I'm going to believe that some backwoods bumpkin beat me.
Neftari: You're in my town, and you're calling me a backwoods bumpkin?
Preá: I'll do whatever I want!
Man with the Red Mask: Tsk, things are getting way out of control.