Luiza: Wait up, guys.
Marcus Vinícius: Hey, see anything?
Neftari: Nothing, as usual.
Luiza: Wait, there's something over there.
Neftari: Where?
Marcus Vinícius: I see it too, behind the tree.
Luiza: Oh no, it's coming towards us!
Neftari: What?
Marcus Vinícius: Was that DEVIL'S PUPPET actually a FantoRob?
Luiza: Well, it just became 200% less interesting.
Neftari: A FantoRob without anyone controlling it must be related to the championship, you know.
Luiza: Is it just me, or was it trying to attack us?
Neftari: No, I don't think so. FantoRob doesn't harm people.
Marcus Vinícius: Well, it's a pretty big FantoRob, and it looks quite damaged.
Neftari: It was practically out of battery.
Marcus Vinícius: Let's take it to the FantoLab. I think I can do some maintenance on it.
Luiza: I'll come with you guys and lend you some spiritual support.
Neftari: Wow, that's heavy...