Marcus Vinícius: And that's it. I didn't think we'd manage, but we did.
Neftari: Never doubt Brazilians and their resourcefulness, but it took so long that Luiza gave up.
Marcus Vinícius: Yeah, she only lasted 5 minutes...
Marcus Vinícius: I was surprised that Arnaldo had an empty and functional FantoDeck.
Neftari: What doesn't Arnaldo have? You could ask for a raspberry-flavored plutonium warhead, and he'd say, "I'll get it from the stock!"
Marcus Vinícius: Hahaha! Seriously... I've never seen such a big and elaborate FantoRob. Is it some kind of new prototype?
Neftari: It must be, or maybe an initial base version, I don't know. All I know is that it's mine now.
Marcus Vinícius: What are you going to name it?
Neftari: What other name would I give it? RogerRob! (RogerRob added to the inventory)