Narrator: TO THE GROUND, TO THE GROUND, TO THE GROUND!
Narrator: DIEGO BRANDÃO MAKES HISTORY IN THE TOURNAMENT.
Narrator: THE WONDER ROOKIE BREAKS PREÁ'S WINNING STREAK!
Preá: But, THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
Narrator: HE CAN’T HOLD BACK HIS EMOTION, HIS FRIENDS RUN TO EMBRACE HIM!
Neftari: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
Luiza: Congratulations, NEF, I doubted you so much!
Neftari: What?
Marcus Vinícius: You really deserved it, buddy, you crushed it in that last battle!
Narrator: THE CROWD GOES WILD WITH THIS FINAL!
Narrator: Preá doesn't seem too happy, does he?
Narrator: Quite understandable, right?
Narrator: NOW HE'S GOING UP THERE TO CLAIM WHAT HE CAME FOR TODAY!
Narrator: HE'S GOING TO RAISE THE FANTOCUP!
Dasdores: You'll regret this.
Neftari: You’ll regret this! Mr. Oswaldo heard everything! I’m going to raise that cup, and he’s going to expose you to everyone!
Juliano: Congratulations, kid, I have to admit I was rooting for you today!
Oswaldo: AHAHAHAHAAHAH, KID! That day I saw you fighting at the store's doorstep.
Oswaldo: I was sure I had found a unique talent.
Oswaldo: But a first-time champion? I could never have imagined! And you even helped me catch Dasdores!
Oswaldo: Go on, raise the FantoCup, you really deserved it!
NARRATOR: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA WHAT!
NARRATOR: WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE, HELP! SOMEONE CALL THE POLICE!
Red Mask: I ask everyone to stay calm, please pay attention!
Red Mask: There's a bomb in this gym, and if anyone tries to escape, we will detonate it!
Red Mask: We've sealed all the exits; there's no way to flee!
Red Mask: If everyone obeys what we say, everything will be fine! Keep your heads down, stay silent.
Dasdores: What is this? What does this mean? I didn't order you to do this!
FantoMask: You’re coming with us!
FantoMask: Grab the champion and his friends.
Luiza: HELP!
Neftari: I... please...