???: Allow me to introduce myself; my name is Leonidas, and I am the creator of the machine circus.
Neftari: Nice to meet you; my name is Neftari, and these are Marcus and Luiza.
Marcus: Hi.
Luiza: Does that mean you're rich?
Leonidas: Haha, I wish!
Leonidas: Neftari, as you can imagine, I know a lot about robots in general. I can help you perform well in the championship.
Neftari: How?
Leonidas: I saw you in battle; you have a lot of potential, but you're too aggressive. That might work in street battles.
Leonidas: But in the championship, the level is high, and without a good strategy and customization, you won't get far.
Leonidas: I've already studied FantoRobs and followed previous championships, and I guarantee you, with my tips, you might even become a champion!
Neftari: I'm interested, but what do you get out of this?
Leonidas: Publicity! I help you, you become famous, and you take the opportunity to thank me for the help and talk about how fabulous the machine circus is!
Neftari: I see, well, I have nothing to lose, so deal!
Leonidas: Great, there's just one catch; I won't tell you everything right away. I have a lot to teach you, and it would overwhelm you.
Leonidas: Let's do it this way every time you win a challenge, come back here, and I'll teach you something new.
Neftari: Sounds good.
Leonidas: Well, Pedro, for the first challenge, I'm going to explain everything about battle.