João: But how is this possible? How? But...
João: I... You??
João: THIS... THIS IS UNFAIR... YOU ALWAYS...
João: I, I was so sure, I... you...
João: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH! YOU'LL PAY FOR THIS, VICCARI!
Neftari: Once again, too much bravado for too little battle.
Neftari: There’s always next year for you to try, but I wouldn’t get my hopes up...
Narrator: DIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIIEGO BRANDÃO EMERGES VICTORIOUS FROM ONE OF THE MOST ABSURD MOMENTS OF THIS FINAL!
Narrator: AND QUALIFIES FOR THE FINAL WHERE HE WILL FACE NONE OTHER THAN PREÁ! WATCH OUT FOR THE EGG, DIEGO!
Neftari: (Humiliating enemies is an underrated feeling. I'm feeling great!)