Female Voice: IT'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS! ALWAYS LIKE THIS! NEXT TIME, I'M GONNA SLAP YOUR MOTHER IN THE FACE!
Male Voice: IF YOU WANT TO DO THAT, YOU'LL HAVE TO GO THROUGH ME FIRST!
Female Voice: I'LL BREAK YOUR FACE AND THEN HERS!
Luiza: Mister Jocleide is out of control; it's about time she gets a lesson, maybe spend about 5 days away from home.
Neftari: I can't blame her; he doesn't let her hang out with her best friend, Arbusta.
Luiza: Arbusta just wants to fit in; I saw her telling the census lady she had a washing machine when she only has a washtub.
João Bertinazzi: Is mister Jocleide and Mrs. Mendra fighting again?
Luiza: It's a continuation from last week's fight.
Male Voice: I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE; BECAUSE OF YOU, I LOST A CAR!
Female Voice: AND WHERE WERE YOU GOING TO PUT THE CAR? ON YOUR MOTHER'S HEAD?
Male Voice: I WAS GOING TO TAKE THE CAR AND RUN YOU OVER, IT'D BE EASY WITH HOW FAT YOU'VE GOTTEN!
Neftari: What's the car story?
Luiza: There was going to be a pool tournament at Mr. Fluário's bar, 
Luiza: and the first prize was a 1993 1.6 Monza with two bullet holes.
João: Mister Jocleide is the best pool player at the bar; he would've definitely won.
Luiza: But Mrs. Mendra didn't let him participate; such an injustice.
Marcus Vinícius: Well, she was taking care of her aunt who had diarrhea.
Neftari: Guys, they went silent.
Luiza: Uai? Did it end? Come on, I want to hear the continuation!
Mrs. Mendra: ARE YOU LISTENING TO WHAT'S GOING ON HERE AT HOME!
Luiza: Run, people, RUN!
???: I need a definitive answer.
Grumpy Man: I've already given my definitive answer, and it's NO.
???: I'm going to insist that you reconsider. Don't you have a desire for justice?
???: Don't you want to give them back everything they did to you?
???: They used you as a pawn in their battles and now discard you like a nobody.
???: You put your life in the front line and what did you get back?
Grumpy Man: I'm.... errr.
???: I know why you hate FantoRobs so much.
Neftari: Get out of here, dude!
Neftari: Oops, sorry, sir!
???: You, I'll get back at you!
Neftari: What?
???: ...Well, you're welcome; I was responding to the gentleman who thanked me!
???: We'll wait for your return with the 2 gigas package.
Grumpy Man: Alright, I'm coming back!
Grumpy Man: Excuse me...
Luiza: Uai what's gotten into him? All polite out of the blue, right, Nef?
Neftari: (Hmm... is there a corner in this city where they're not infiltrated?)