Neftari:Done.
Arnaldo: That was quick, huh? I thought it would take a few days.
Arnaldo: So I guess after this, you'll go look for the talent scout there, but before that, I have to explain something to you. See that lady over there?
Letícia: Hi, folks!
Arnaldo: Her name is LETÍCIA. She assembles FantoRobs and PHYSICAL CORES. When you need a new one, just bring the necessary parts and money to her.
Neftari: Alright, but how am I going to get those parts?
Arnaldo: Neftari, you're going to enter the championship; the more battles you win, the more parts and money you'll receive, trust me.
Arnaldo: Well, it's time to fulfill my part of the deal.