Man with a red mask: ...stick to the plan. Stay here and keep an eye on this case with the valves.
Man with a gray mask: For how long?
Man with a red mask: Until the champion is defeated. You’ll get a signal.
Man with a gray mask: Do we really have to do this kind of thing?
Man with a red mask: You know the malware was stolen, and we still haven't found it. Until we have it back, we need to keep cooperating
Man with a gray mask: But why won't we redo it?
Man with a red mask: It takes too much time, it would seriously delay our plan... As I said, we’ll keep cooperating.
Man with a red mask: There's a FantoBed nearby that was "placed." Use it if you need to.
Man with a red mask: I've also placed some of our people in the middle of the challenge to take down a few participants and make it easier for you.
Man with a gray mask: Understood.
Man with a red mask: I'd better not risk being seen. I’ll take the forest route out