???: ... challenge?
???: Not yet, I was helping to look, but it’s tough.
???: Looking for a specific FantoRob in this city in the middle of the tournament is worse than looking for a needle in a haystack!
???: It was pretty easy, most of the people have poorly thought-out FantoRobs; the bad part is having to deal with something else more important to find.
???: Makes sense, it does seem like a waste of time, but the mission is bigger than this.
???: Tsk, why did they have to lose the malware right now?
???: I know, without it, we can't expose the Devil behind the Fantomask.
???: DON'T SAY THAT OUT LOUD!
???: Oops, my bad!
???: Let's get out of here; it’s better if we don’t discuss these things in a place like this.
???: True.
Marcus Vinícius: There's nothing about "Tesourado" here, just some internet technicians.
Neftari: Did you understand what they were talking about?
Marcus Vinícius: Not really, we only caught half of the conversation.
Luiza: It doesn’t matter! I’m gonna go beat that country bumpkin down right now!
Neftari: Man, he keeps talking about "Tesourado" and never says what it actually is, I’m mad too!
Marcus Vinícius: Let’s go right now.
Neftari: ... Ué?