Aunt Ana: Were you watching FantoRob videos again?
Neftari: Yeah, I was watching this year's finals.
Aunt Ana: Let's eat dinner; it's getting cold.
Neftari: Getting cold in this heat?
Neftari: Aren't we supposed to wait until midnight to have Christmas dinner?
Aunt Ana: Oh no, I'm hungry. I always thought that tradition was silly.
Neftari: Well, let's eat then.
Aunt Ana: But before that, I think there's a little something for you under the Christmas tree.