Neftari: GI... GIRINOROB
Neftari: How did you know that's the one I wanted, Aunt Ana?
Aunt Ana: Haha, you never stop talking about these things.
Neftari: But you said you didn't have the money.
Aunt Ana: I saved a little from my pension, but that doesn't matter; let's eat.
Neftari: I'm going to send a photo to Marcus now!
Aunt Ana: Neftari, it's time to ea...
Aunt Ana: ...
Aunt Ana: Oh, these kids...