Neftari: I heard you had a fight with Arbusta.
Luiza: Yeah, I did. She had the volume up so high; I couldn't even hear my own thoughts!
Neftari: Oh, really? How did it go?
Luiza: Nothing special. I just yelled, "Hey, turn the volume down, it's way too loud!"
Luiza: Then she said, "I'm in my own house, I have the right!"
Luiza: So I replied, "You don't have the right to disturb everyone here. What are you celebrating? Did your husband stop cheating on you?"
Luiza: Then he chimed in with, "Oh, you rude girl, show some respect, blah blah blah, you don't know my life!"
Luiza: So I told her, "I really don't, but maybe the pamonheira redhead does!"
Luiza: Then she started going on about how I was just jealous of her life!
Luiza: I told her, "Yeah, I'm totally jealous of your poorly made house that looks like a cheap soap opera set."
Neftari: Did she say anything else?
Luiza: She grumbled for a while, but after about 10 minutes, they turned the music off.