Marcus Vinícius: Nef, any problem?
Neftari: Dude, I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
Marcus Vinícius: I'm happy for you; I don't understand much about battles, but I'll try to help you with the FantoRob setup!
Neftari: Thanks, I'll need it; I'm also going to need some tea to sleep tonight, I'm so excited!
Marcus Vinícius: In Mandioquinha, we had a tea we made with KICHAKOTA herbs...
Neftari: You can tell me later.
Marcus Vinícius: Hey!