Augusto: Hey, buddy, did you manage to win the challenge?
Neftari: It was a bit tough, but yes, I did. How about you?
Augusto: Unfortunately, no. I was doing really well, but I ended up having a problem.
Neftari: What happened?
Augusto: It's kind of complicated to explain.
Neftari: What do you mean?
Augusto: It's because... I'll explain another time.
Neftari: Come on, I won't tell anyone, I promise!
Augusto: Have you happened to see someone with a red mask during the challenge?
Neftari: Red mask? Yes, I did, and there was another one with a gray mask. Aren't they part of the event staff?
Augusto: Some of them are, but can I give you some advice?
Neftari: Of course!
Augusto: There's a legend in the FantoRob Championship about someone with a red mask who appears to sabotage participants. They call it the "Crimson Mask."
Augusto: It's a legend known among the veterans, even though the FantoRob Company has never said anything about it, and nothing has been proven.
Augusto: If you happen to see someone like that, it's better to avoid confrontation.
Neftari: Okay... (that's a strange story) sure, I'll try to remember that.