Neftari: What do you intend to accomplish by walking like this? Dig a hole to the floor below and escape?
Dasdores: Hahaha, clever one.
Neftari: I don't understand why you're stuck here. Aren't you the Red Maks, their leader?
Dasdores: It's not that simple. They used to be my subordinates, but it seems Iracema turned them against me.
Dasdores: Now, I don't understand. Her trying to oust me from the betting scheme is one thing.
Dasdores: But a bomb, terrorism? Where is that tramp trying to go with this?
Neftari: What if it's not her?
Dasdores: Who else could it be? Unless he...
Dasdores: Someone's coming.
FantoMask 1: You're coming with us. If you behave, you won't get hurt.
FantoMask 2: Quick, come with me!
Dasdores: Finally, someone loyal to me.
FantoMask 2: There's still a core loyal to you, but we don't have time for this now. Let's go!
Dasdores: Wait, what's Iracema's plan?
FantoMask 2: There's really no time to explain now!
FantoMask 2: They'll figure out what happened soon, and they'll come after us!
Dasdores: Oh, no, it's better if we split up. It'll be easier for them to catch us otherwise.
Dasdores: I'll go this way, you go left. Go!
Neftari: ...