Iracema: What did you guys do?
Masked Man: I should be asking you, what did you do?
Iracema: Did you happen to see me leave my place?
Iracema: It must have been related to the blockage of the last key you forced.
Masked Man: What do you mean?
Iracema: : It might have triggered some alert. I'll reboot, come on, get out of here!
Masked Man: What? Why?
Iracema: If this alert calls someone, they'll come here and see the mess!
Iracema: I'd like to see you explain this to your boss!
Masked Man: Let's get out of here, hurry.
Masked Man: It's time of my revange.
Masked Man: You, I'll get you back. Just wait!
Iracema:  Hehehehe, we gave those thugs a scare.
Neftari: Hahaha, that was awesome!
Iracema: Yes Finally!
Neftari: And what were they doing here?
Iracema: Preventing someone from reaching the last key before Preá.
Neftari: What's your connection with the Red Mask?
Iracema: Diego Brandão, right? We can talk later, and I'll tell you everything. For now, you need to go!
Iracema: I rebooted the system, which will unlock the last key for you.
Iracema: Go quickly before they return and block it again.
Iracema: Take a gift from me for helping me deal with those ruffians.
Iracema: (Hands you Special Skeleton)
Iracema: When you finish your challenge, meet me at the FantoLab, and I'll explain things further.