Narrator: WE HAVE ARRIVED, MY FRIENDS, WE HAVE ARRIVED!
Narrator: We have reached the final showdown. After this battle, we will discover WHO IS THIS YEAR'S CHAMPION!
Narrator: On one side, the rookie wonder, the one who shook the championship this summer, Diego Brandão!
Narrator: Will he put an end to Preá's reign?
Oswaldo: Nef, we don’t have much time, but I heard everything. GO OUT THERE AND WIN, TRUST ME!
Neftari: Okay, okay!
Narrator: And entering on the other side, the one who made history in this championship, the three-time champion PREÁ!
Narrator: He said he's not ready to give up the crown as king of FantoRob yet!
Preá: You made it this far. I admit, I’m impressed. You got lucky too, huh.
Preá: But I'm going to make you pay for the audacity of daring to challenge me like you did in the Center!
Neftari: ...
Narrator: Wow, Diego Brandão looks really tense, this isn’t good!
Neftari: (I won't lose).
Narrator: WITHOUT FURTHER ADO, THE CROWD IS GOING CRAZY TO SEE THIS FIGHT!
Narrator: FIGHT!