Juliano: Good morning, everyone. I can see that you're all very excited!
Juliano: For me, it's an honor and a joy to be here entrusted with opening another summer championship!
Juliano: Every year is a rush; we always want to raise the bar, we always want to outdo ourselves and make a better championship than the previous one.
Juliano: I can say that our efforts have paid off; we are already the largest audience and the most talked-about topic on the internet throughout the summer in Brazil!
Oswaldo: Do you know him?
Neftari: Of course! It's Juliano Arbô; he invented the FantoRobs!
Oswaldo: That's right, one of the greatest geniuses in robotics in the world. And a very humble guy, in my personal opinion.
Oswaldo: Róger, my friend, good to see ya!
Caseiro Róger: Oh, Dr. Oswaldo, how ya doin'?
Oswaldo: All's just fine, my good friend! Came here to watch the opening?
Caseiro Róger: Me? Nah, I'm investigatin' the DEVIL'S PUPPET.
Luiza: DEVIL'S PUPPET?
Caseiro Róger: Uai, ever heard of it?
Marcus Vinícius: I never have!
Neftari: Me neither.
Caseiro Róger: Well, let me tell ya. I was out there on my farm, takin' care of my cows.
Caseiro Róger: Then all of a sudden, I heard somethin' like this: TCHUC TCHUC TCHUC.
Luiza: Tchuc?
Caseiro Róger: Yep, just like that. So I hollered, 
Caseiro Róger: OH MY GOODNESS WHO'S THERE?
Caseiro Róger: Then I heard somethin' like glorp glorp.
Caseiro Róger: So I said, 
Caseiro Róger: "WHKDAHFU DISPELL!"
Marcus Vinícius: Is anyone followin' this?
Caseiro Róger: Hold on, I'm gettin' to it!
Caseiro Róger: Then it went like this
Caseiro Róger: EEEEEEEK EEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEK.
Caseiro Róger: And right there in front of me... right there in front of me...
Caseiro Róger: ... ...
Neftari: DEVIL'S PUPPET?
Caseiro Róger: A painted jaguar!
Neftari: Wait, the painted jaguar was the DEVIL'S PUPPET?
Caseiro Róger: DEVIL'S PUPPET? Oh no, that's a whole 'nother story!
Marcus: But?
Oswaldo: We'd best cut this conversation short; the ceremony's nearly over.
Juliano: ... I thank y'all for puttin' in the effort to make this happen. I hope everyone has a great time, and may the best one win!
Luiza: But what about the DEVIL'S PUPPET?
Caseiro Róger: Meet me at the central park, and I'll show y'all!
Marcus: Hey, wait, he's gone.
Oswaldo: Well, Neftari, the first challenge is open, and the ceremony's over.
Oswaldo: If you need anything, just find me at the FantoRob Tower.
Neftari: Alright.
Oswaldo: Make good use of that letter I gave ya, now!
Neftari: I'll do my best!
Neftari: Oh, I'm so nervous.
Luiza: Well, you don't need to think too hard; worst-case scenario, you'll just embarrass yourself on national television.
Marcus: Luiza!