Marcus Vinícius: Nef, Mr. Leonidas sent for you at the Machinery Circus.
Neftari: Good morning first, right?
Luiza: Good morning. Mr. Leonidas sent for you at the Machinery Circus.
Neftari: What does he want with me?
Luiza: Well, I don't know. I guess that's why he called you.
Neftari: Yeah, you're right. Let's go.
Girl: It's the DEVIL'S PUPPET it's the DEVIL'S PUPPET!
Boy: Ruuuuuuun!
Marcus Vinícius: These kids just won't let go of this DEVIL'S PUPPET story, huh?