Reporter: Here he is, finally, Diego Brandão, a word please?
Neftari: Uh, what's going on?
Reporter: Would you say you feel betrayed by the participant João Bertinazzi?
Angry Man: Don't mind that, Diego, you'll get back at him in the final!
Angry Woman: Sneaky snake, you only got back what you did to poor Preá!
Neftari: Hey, calm down, I didn't...
Boy: You'll never beat João in a 1v1!
Reporter: So, what's your opinion on what happened? Do you regret what you did to Preá? Do you feel unjustly treated?
Oswaldo: He's not saying anything now!
Oswaldo: Come on, kid, come with me!