João: What do you think this is?
Neftari: I don't know, it looks like some sort of control center, but let's keep our voices down.
João: It's the guys from earlier, from the cave, they're operating the computers.
João: What do you think this means?
Neftari: If this is where they control the challenge, it makes sense now.
João: What do you mean?
Neftari: They're controlling the house, that's why I can't find the last key.
João: YOU'RE ALREADY ON THE LAST KEY.
Neftari: Speak quietly, man, speak quietly, they'll hear us.
Iracema: Hey, you guys, you shouldn't be in here!
Neftari: João, run!
Iracema: Wait! Wait! I recognize your voice, you're from the challenge!
Iracema: I need one of you to do me a favor, or you'll never get the last key!
Neftari: Me, but... okay, okay.
Iracema: See that button on the other side of the room?
Iracema: Go there and press it, easy, right?
Neftari: But there are so many people here, how am I going to get there?
Iracema: The room is dark, and they're focused. You're still dressed as a ghost. If you move slowly, no one will see you.
Neftari: I, I...
Iracema: Do you want the last key or not?
Neftari: Okay!