Narrator: And now we've reached one of the most anticipated moments of this edition!
Narrator: The two main characters of an unprecedented rivalry will finally settle their scores!
Narrator: On one side, we have Bertizzeira!
Narrator: Will he prove his superiority to everyone?
João: Finally, Viccari! Today is the moment of our final showdown!
João: This time, I won't go easy on you hehehehe! Today is the day to prove to everyone that I'm the best master!
Narrator: On the other side, we have Diego Brandão!
Narrator: This is his moment in the championship; will he make Bertizzeira pay for the betrayal in the seventh challenge?
Neftari: Hmm... You know, in this past week, I had a lot of time to reevaluate our battles throughout the summer.
Neftari: I noticed a pattern; you always challenged me when I was at a disadvantage, never the other way around!
Neftari: You're a snitch! I should have never trusted you! You talk too much...
Neftari: And as my aunt always says: "Those who talk too much say goodbye to the horse!"
Narrator: With this proverb, we move on to what everyone wants to see!
Narrator: FIGHT!